Wait,
I won't tie a rakhi,
I'll tell you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, isn't
this true? If I want
to get Priya, I have to escape today somehow
.  Ray, I'm not ready yet. It's
time for school.
Mom, I'm not going to school today.
I'm not going to go. That's all.
Ray, don't play games and go to school.
How can I tell you, my mother, that's not my problem, is
n't it? Today is Rakhi festival,
girls tie Rakhi at school, so what's wrong with you, my
brother, going?
You tie Rakhi for 10 rupees and get ₹1
.  We have money, but we have
feelings.
Now you're going to school, do you want me to
tell your father?  Mom, please, Mom, what's wrong?
He says he's going to school because girls tie rakhis at school.
Hey, how much pain do you have to go through to tie a rakhi?
You also come to our school and see if
our English teacher will tie a rakhi for you.
My father is scared. I am still going. I am going. I am going.